1. randomEmail = custom.RandomData.generateRandomEmail()
5. randomFirstName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomFirstName()
9. randomLastName = custom.RandomData.generateRandomLastName()
13. randomPhone = custom.RandomData.generateRandomPhone()
17. randomAddress = custom.RandomData.generateRandomAddress()
21. randomCode = custom.RandomData.generateRandomCode()
25. openBrowser("")
29. setViewPortSize(1920, 1080)
33. navigateToUrl(URL)
37. custom.BrowserHelper.setupBrowserWindow()
41. waitForPageLoad(30)
45. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/header_digibox"), 30)
49. waitForElementClickable(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Search/icon-search"), 30)
53. enhancedClick(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Search/icon-search"))
57. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Search/field-search"), 30)
61. setText(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Search/field-search"), "IPHONE 13 PRO MAX SIERRA BLUE 128GB")
65. sendKeys(findTestObject("WEB/Home Page/Search/field-search"), Keys.chord(ENTER))
69. waitForPageLoad(30)
73. delay(3)
77. custom.ProductHelper.addAnyAvailableProduct()
1. status = testCaseContext.getTestCaseStatus()
5. if (status == "PASSED")
2. saveScreenshot("FAILED")
1. try
1. tcName = getTestCaseName()
1. return com.kms.katalon.core.configuration.RunConfiguration.getExecutionSourceName().replace(Test Cases/, ).replaceAll([\\/:*?"<>|], _)
5. folderPath = Screenshot/$status/$tcName/
9. Files.createDirectories(Paths.get(folderPath))
13. screenshotPath = $folderPath$status_$this.getTimestamp().png
1. return new java.text.SimpleDateFormat(yyyyMMdd_HHmmss).format(new java.util.Date())
17. takeScreenshot(screenshotPath)
21. println("Screenshot saved : " + screenshotPath)
6. saveHtmlSource("FAILED")
1. try
1. tcName = getTestCaseName()
1. return com.kms.katalon.core.configuration.RunConfiguration.getExecutionSourceName().replace(Test Cases/, ).replaceAll([\\/:*?"<>|], _)
5. folderPath = Screenshot/$status/$tcName/
9. Files.createDirectories(Paths.get(folderPath))
13. htmlPath = $folderPath$status_$this.getTimestamp().html
1. return new java.text.SimpleDateFormat(yyyyMMdd_HHmmss).format(new java.util.Date())
17. html = getHtmlSource(OPTIONAL)
2. println("Failed to save HTML source: " + e.getMessage())
9. println(Test Case '$testCaseContext.getTestCaseId()' finished with status: $status)